Register to The Kay Swift Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, 1936-1989; Series IV; 1.5' (3 boxes)
  - Crawford, Cheryl, 1952-1960; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 496)
  - Creative Arts Rehabilitation Center, 1979 Oct. 16; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 496)
  - Crosby, Bing, 1952 Aug. 24; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 496)
  - Crouse, Russell (Box 17, Folder 496)
    see Weissberger, L. Arnold (6/4/54, 6/18/54, 6/25/54 and 6/29/54)
  - Dalrymple, Jean, 1961 May 31; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 496)
  - Darlo, No date; 6 items. (Box 17, Folder 496)
    see also RCA (12/18/61)
  - Davis, Samuel R., 1959 May 1; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 496)
  - Dietz, Lucinda, 1986 June 18; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 497)
  - Dineen, George A., 1958-1962; 8 items. (Box 17, Folder 497)
  - Doll, Bill, 1960-1961; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 497)
  - Dorr, John Van Nostram, 1944-1962; 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 497)
  - Dorr, Nell (Box 17, Folder 497)
    see McBride, Mary Margaret (10/19/54)
  - Dramatists Guild, 1979-1984; 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 497)
  - Dunne, Irene, 1950 Jan. 20; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 497)
  - Eddy, 1959 Jan 9.; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Emigrant Industrial Savings Bank, 1961 June 23; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Erlanger, Michael, 1960; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Fairchild, Kim, 1986; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Farnol, Lynn, 1959-1975; 6 items. (Box 17, Folder 498)
    see also Porgy and Bess lecture tour (21/604)
  - Fitzgerald, Ella, No date; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Flanders, Michael, 1958 Mar. 21; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Fleur and Tom, No date; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Francie, Sept. 30; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Freed, Ralph, 1967 Aug. 1; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 498)
    see also Schulman, John (2/63)
  - Freedley, George, 1953-1958; 11 items. (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Fuller, Nancy Tatnall, 1988 July 29; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - G., David, 1958 Feb. 26; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 499)
  - Galloway, Hunter, 1958; 16 items. (Box 17, Folder 499)
  - Galloway Records, 1955-1957; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 499)
  - Gardiner, Stewart, 1962; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 499)
  - Gartiez, Paul, 1952; 34 items. (Box 17, Folder 500)
  - General Electric, 1959; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 501)
  - George Gershwin Festival (University of Miami), 1970 July 16; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 501)
  - Gershwin, Ira and Lee, 1959-1966; 9 items. (Box 17, Folder 501)
    see also Let 'Em Eat Cake (3/1/63 and 1/73)
  - Gershwin family (Box 17, Folder 501)
    see Rose, Don (1/10/83)
  - Gershwin Publishing Corporation, 1974 June 4; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 501)
  - Gertz, Mitchell, 1952-1959; 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 501)
  - Gibson, William, 1960; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - Gilmore, Eddy, 1958 June 2; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - Ginger, 1986 June 16; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - Gish, Lillian (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - Godden, Rumer, 1958; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - Gould, Ellen, No date; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 502)
    Incomplete
  - Graf, Shirley, 1952; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - Green, Bernie, 1962 July 12; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - Green, Johnny, 1953; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - Green, Stanley, 1986 June 19; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - Hamilton[?], Becky, 1958-1959; 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - Hammerstein, Oscar II, 1959; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - Harms, 1952 Sept. 26; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Harnick, Sheldon, 1986 June 6; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Hart, Morris, 1956 Sept. 26; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Hart, Moss, 1959; 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Hatchards Booksellers, 1961; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - re: Henry, Theodore, 1946 Jan. 21; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Hershon, Red, 1960 Mar. 16; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Heyward, Dorothy Dubose, 1959; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Holm, Celeste, 1980 May; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Holmes, Teddy, 1958 Oct. 7; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Henry Holt and Company, 1953 Mar. 9; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Hollywood, Daniel, 1959 Oct. 2; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 504)
  - Howard, Mel, 1958; 11 items. (Box 17, Folder 504)
  - Howell, Miriam, 1958-1967; 7 items. (Box 17, Folder 504)
  - Hughes, Alice, No date; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 505)
  - Hugo & Luigi Productions, No date; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 505)
  - re: Hunter's Moon, 1958 Feb. 24-26; 15 items. (Box 17, Folder 505)
    (telegrams)
  - Husson, 1958 Aug. 20; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 505)
  - International Creative Management (ICM) (Box 17, Folder 505)
    see Wood, Audrey (6/18/79)
  - Insurance Company of North America, 1958-1961; 7 items. (Box 17, Folder 506)
  - International Committee Against Mental Illness, 1961; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 506)
  - Iran Foundation, 1965; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 506)
  - Jablonsky, Edward, 1957; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 507)
    see also Let 'Em Eat Cake (6/6/62)
  - Jacobs, David, 1958-1959; 16 items. (Box 17, Folder 507)
  - Jaffe, Hy, No date; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 507)
  - James, Donald H., [1950 May 5]; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 507)
  - James, Paul (Box 17, Folder 507)
  - Jessye, Eva Alberta, 1979-1989; 13 items. (Box 17, Folder 508)
  - Johnson, Teddy, 1958; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 508)
  - Jukes, Mary, 1967; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 508)
  - [K...?], Margaret, 1952; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - Kantner, Harold, 1980; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - Kerr, Walter (Box 17, Folder 509)
    see Weissberger, L. Arnold (4/1/55)
  - Kimbrough, Emily, 1956 June 26; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - Knollwood Music, 1960 Nov. 15; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - Kolmar Associates, 1959 Aug.; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - Kramer, Alex, 1966; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - La Bachie, 1962 Jan. 24; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - Lane, Burton, 1966 Mar. 18; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 509)
    see also American Guild of Authors and Composers (AGAC) and Songwriters' Protective Association (SPA) (1/21/58)
  - Lasker, Mary, 1944-1959; 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - Laura, 1958 Aug. 1; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - Laventure, William B., 1958; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - Lee and Skippy, No date; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 510)
  - Leeds Music, 1961-1966; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 510)
  - Lesley, 1958 Feb. 26; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 510)
  - Levin, Kay and Robert, 1960-1961; 10 items. (Box 17, Folder 510)
  - Levine, Maurice, 1986 June 24; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 510)
  - Levy, Mrs., 1958 Sept. 16; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 510)
  - Levy, Ben, 1958 May 1; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 510)
  - Library of Congress. Copyright Office, 1953-1957; 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 510)
  - Life, 1944 June 2; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 511)
  - Lighthouse (Box 17, Folder 511)
    see Mrs. St[?]alem (4/24/72)
  - Lillie, Beatrice (Box 17, Folder 511)
    see Weissberger, L. Arnold (6/25/54)
  - Linden, Bella L., 1959 Jan. 8; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 511)
  - Lindsay, Howard, 1960 Apr. 28; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 511)
  - Lipkin, Mack, Dr., 1959 May 21; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 511)
  - Littler, Emile, 1958 Apr. 8; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 511)
  - Logan, Josh (Box 17, Folder 511)
    see Weissberger, L. Arnold (2/11/54 and 3/11/54)
  - Louise, 1964 Feb. 28; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 511)
  - MacColdman, No date; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 511)
  - Joseph Maharam Foundation, 1970 Sept. 29; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 511)
  - March, Freddie, 1961 Dec. 24; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 511)
  - Marcucci, 1961 Jan. 4; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 511)
  - Edward B. Marks Music, 1958-1966; 8 items. (Box 17, Folder 511)
  - Marks, Gerald, 1986 June 19; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 511)
  - Martin, Ernest H., 1955 Dec. 13; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 512)
  - Mary, 1960 Dec. 28; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 512)
  - Maryland Center for Public Broadcasting, 1984 Aug. 21; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 512)
  - McBride, Mary Margaret, 1954 Oct. 19; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 512)
  - McCaffrey, William, 1962; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 512)
  - McCloy, John J., 1958; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 512)
  - McKay, Jill, 1967; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 512)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1985 Oct. 4; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 512)
  - Mercer, Johnny, 1967; 7 items. (Box 17, Folder 512)
    see also Songwriters' Hall of Fame
  - Meridian Theatrical, 1983 July 12; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 512)
  - Merv, 1959 Oct. 3; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 513)
  - Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer (M.G.M.), 1947-1963; 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 513)
  - Miles, Bernard, 1958 Feb. 26; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 513)
  - Montague, Paul, 1960 Dec. 15; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 513)
  - William Morris Agency, 1949-1955; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 513)
  - Murphy, Owen (Box 17, Folder 513)
    see Weissberger, L. Arnold (2/6/56)
  - Music Performance Trust Fund, 1955-1964; 18 items. (Box 17, Folder 514)
    re: Galloway Records
  - Music Publishers Holding Corporation, 1959-1967; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 515)
  - National Broadcasting Company (NBC), 1936, 1960-61; 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 515)
  - National Telefilm Associates, 1961; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 515)
  - New York Association for the Blind, 1959; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 515)
    re: The Lighthouse
  - New York Heart Association, No date; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 515)
  - New York Herald Tribune, 1966 Apr. 25; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 515)
  - New York (State). Department of Labor, 1966 June 20; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 515)
  - The New Yorker (Box 17, Folder 515)
    see Schulman, John (8/3/71)
  - Nicholls, Don and Gee, 1960; 4 items. (Box 17, Folder 515)
  - Norddeutscher Rundfunk. Funkhaus Hannover, 1961; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 515)
  - Oppenheimer, George, 1949 July; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - Orenstein, Debra and John, 1986 Nov. 1; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - Paley, Emily, 1986 Oct. 26; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - Palmer, Carleton H., 1936 Aug. 4; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - Pan American World Airways, 1970 Feb. 4; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - Parker, L., 1976; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - Pavlini, Alex, 1961 Feb. 9; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - Paysner, Betty, 1960 Dec. 11; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - Peloquin, Lennyce, 1970 Apr. 22; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - Perry, Frank, 1959; 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - Phillips, Jimmy, 1958 Aug.; 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - Pryor, Arthur Jr., 1936 Aug. 7; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 516)
  - RKO Radio Pictures, 1944-1950; 17 items. (Box 18, Folder 517)
    re: mostly Never a Dull Moment
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA), 1955-1962; 11 items. (Box 18, Folder 518)
    see also Century 21 (19/563)
  - Reba, 1959 July 3; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 518)
  - Reiskind, Edwin M., 1964 Nov. 2; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 518)
  - Reynolds, Oliver C., 1957-1961; 4 items. (Box 18, Folder 518)
  - Rod, 1958; 4 items. (Box 18, Folder 519)
  - Rodgers and Hammerstein Concert Library (Box 18, Folder 519)
    see Rose, Don (1982)
  - Romeike Press Clippings, 1959-1960; 8 items. (Box 18, Folder 519)
  - Ronny, No date; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 519)
  - Rose, Billy, 1965 July 25; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 519)
  - Rose, Don, 1970-1993; 21 items. (Box 18, Folder 520)
    see also Gershwin, Ira (4/7/78) and Let 'Em Eat Cake (x/x)
  - Rosenberg, Anna M., Aug. 7; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 521)
  - Rosenberg, Sylvia, 1959 Oct. 1; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 521)
  - Ross, Steve, No date; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 521)
  - [Rowell], Ann, 1986 June 16; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 521)
  - Ruby, Harry, 1966 Feb. 17; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 521)
  - Ruth, 1951-1959; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 521)
  - Samson Music, 1960-1970; 44 items. (Box 18, Folder 522)
    see also Schulman, John (1960)
  - S[...?], Paul, No date; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 523)
  - Sayre, [Joel], 1958 Apr. 24; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 523)
  - Scherman, Thomas, 1960 Sept. 8; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 523)
  - Scheuer, Lewis M., 1959; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 523)
  - Schloss, Stanley, 1959 Oct. 28; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 523)
  - Schulman, John, 1957-1960; 18 items. (Box 18, Folder 524)
  - Schulman, John, 1961-1967; 49 items. (Box 18, Folder 525)
  - Schulman, John, 1968-1971; 43 items. (Box 18, Folder 526)
  - Scribner's Book Store, 1971 Feb. 27; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 527)
  - Severns, B. Scott, 1966 Mar. 2; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 527)
  - Shapiro, Dave, 1961 Apr. 25; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 527)
  - Shawnee Mission School, 1973 Feb. 7; 9 items. (Box 18, Folder 527)
  - Sheaffer, Louis, No date; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 527)
  - Shearn, 1959 June 19; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 527)
  - Schirmer, Mabel (Box 18, Folder 527)
    see Let 'Em Eat Cake (12/9/77)
  - Shilkret, Nathaniel (Box 18, Folder 527)
    see Paris '90 (12/20/51 and 3/31/52)
  - Short, Bobby, 1986 Oct. 14; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 527)
  - Shubert, Milton I., 1949-1950; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 527)
  - Silvers, Phil (Box 18, Folder 527)
    see Weissberger, L. Arnold (10/14/54)
  - Skinner, Cornelia Otis (Box 18, Folder 527)
    see Crosby, Bing; Paris '90; and Joseph Maharam Foundation (9/29/70)
  - Smith, Don, 1986 Oct 14; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 527)
  - Sondheim, Stephen, 1986 June 19; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 528)
  - Songwriters' Hall of fAME, 1970-1979; 6 items. (Box 18, Folder 528)
  - Songwriters of America, 1957 Mar. 25; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 528)
  - Songwriters' Protective Association (SPA), 1950-1966; 15 items. (Box 18, Folder 528)
    see also American Guild of Authors and Composers (AGAC)
  - Mrs. St[?]alem, 1972 Apr. 23; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 529)
    incomplete
  - Stanley, Minerva, 1960; 8 items. (Box 18, Folder 529)
  - Stern, Alfred, 1959-1986; 16 items. (Box 18, Folder 529)
    see also Schulman, John (6/26/61) and Joseph Maharam Foundation (9/29/70)
  - Sterne, Tracey, 1987 Apr. 9; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 530)
  - Stevens, Roger (Box 18, Folder 530)
    see Weissberger, L. Arnold (9/9/54, 10/7/54, 11/18/54 and 1/20/55)
  - Steward, E. Sheldon, 1951 Dec. 13; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 530)
  - Steward, Lawrence D., 1959 Nov. 27; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 530)
    see also Let 'Em Eat Cake (6/22/62)
  - Stillman, Al, 1958 Mar. 11; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 530)
  - Stires, Ernest, No date; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 530)
  - Strong, Walter, 1960 Jan. 25; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 530)
  - Swaine, Adeney Brigg, 1961 Oct. 13; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 530)
  - Taylor, Davidson, 1950; 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 530)
  - Taylor, Robert Lewis, 1949-1961; 17 items. (Box 18, Folder 530)
    see also Clark, Bobby (1948 Jan. 1)
  - Theatre Guild (Box 18, Folder 530)
    see Freedley, George (1953 Jan. 7)
  - Thompson Banks Productions, No date; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - Thompson, Harlan Howard, No date; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - Townsend, Reginald T., 1936 July 29; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - Twigs, No date; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - Unidentified, No date; 4 items. (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - U.S. National Bank of Portland, 1944; 7 items. (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - United States. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1971-1972; 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - United States. Department of State, 1962 Aug. 28; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - Unity Centre of Christianity, 1958 July 18; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - Vaumoron-Ellis, Jeannine, 1971 Feb. 16; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - Verterans Administration, 1958; 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - Verve Records (Box 18, Folder 531)
    see Fitzgerald, Ella
  - Vogel, Fred G., 1981 Mar. 16; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - Warburg, Bettina, Dr., No date; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 532)
    see also Iran Foundation
  - Warburg, James P., 1956; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 532)
    see also Paul James
  - Waring, Fred, 1952; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 532)
  - Warner Bros. Music, 1970-1971; 4 items. (Box 18, Folder 532)
  - Warner, Russell, 1989 July 19; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 532)
  - Waugh, Alec[?], 1952 May 19; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 532)
  - WCBS-TV (New York), 1949 Aug. 24; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 532)
  - Weedy, Robert (Box 18, Folder 532)
    see Samson Music (5/22/62)
  - Weissberger, L. Arnold, 1952-1953; 35 items. (Box 18, Folder 533)
  - Weissberger, L. Arnold, 1954; 69 items. (Box 18, Folder 534)
  - Weissberger, L. Arnold, 1955; 47 items. (Box 18, Folder 535)
  - Weissberger, L. Arnold, 1956-1958; 29 items. (Box 19, Folder 536)
    see also Cotes, Peter (1958)
  - Weissberger, L. Arnold, 1959-1980; 31 items. (Box 19, Folder 537)
    see also Rose, Don (1978)
  - Whitely, William F., 1944 June 23; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 538)
  - Whitney, John Hay, No date; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 538)
  - Williams, Ursula Vaughan (Box 19, Folder 538)
    see Schulman, John (12/15/70)
  - Wood, Audrey, 1979 June 18; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 538)
  - Wood, Peggy, 1952 May 20; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 538)
  - Wray, William Henry, 1975; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 538)
  - Wurlitzer, Bruck, 1986 Oct. 24; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 538)
  - Yadon, Amber (Box 19, Folder 538)
    see Shawnee Mission School (2/7/73)
- Business and Financial Records, 1946-1989; Series V; 1.25' (3 boxes)
  This series consists of financial records, royalty statements, bills, and receipts. Also included are folders of materials relating to individual theatrical projects. Folders are arranged alphabetically by name of institution or project, then chronologically within the same folder name.
  - All About Elsie (Box 19, Folder 539)
    Correspondence and miscellaneous material
  - American Federation of Musicians (AF of M) (Box 19, Folder 540)
    Miscellaneous material
  - American Guild of Authors and Composers (AGAC) (Box 19, Folder 541)
    Contract
  - American Guild of Authors and Composers (AGAC), 1950s (Box 19, Folder 542)
    Collection of royalties plan
  - American Guild of Authors and Composers (AGAC), 1960s (Box 19, Folder 543)
  - American Guild of Authors and Composers (AGAC), 1970s (Box 19, Folder 544)
  - American Guild of Authors and Composers (AGAC), 1980 Jan. 10 (Box 19, Folder 545)
    Minutes form for a meeting of the Writers Nomination Committee
  - American Guild of Authors and Composers (AGAC) (Box 19, Folder 546)
  - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP) (Box 19, Folder 547)
    Check stubs
  - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP) (Box 19, Folder 548)
    Collection of Royalties Plan Authorization
  - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP) (Box 19, Folder 549)
    Memorandum
  - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP), 1940s (Box 19, Folder 550)
    Royalty statements
  - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP), 1950s (Box 19, Folder 551)
  - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP), 1960s (Box 19, Folder 552)
  - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP), 1970s (Box 19, Folder 553)
  - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP), 1980s (Box 19, Folder 554)
  - American Academy of Dramatic Arts, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 555)
    Receipts for donations
  - Apartment leases (Box 19, Folder 556)
  - Associated Music-Copy Service Corp. (Box 19, Folder 557)
    Bills
  - Banking (Box 19, Folder 558)
  - Book Travel Bureau (Box 19, Folder 559)
    Airline ticket envelop
  - British Broadcasting System (Box 19, Folder 560)
    Statement of payment for interview about George Gershwin
  - Berger, Leon (Box 19, Folder 561)
  - CBS News, 1962 July 11 (Box 19, Folder 562)
  - Century 21 (Box 19, Folder 563)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank (Box 19, Folder 564)
    Promissory note
  - Chappell, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 565)
    Statement of royalties
  - Chappell (Box 19, Folder 566)
    Agreement (incomplete)
  - Check stubs, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 567)
  - Check stubs, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 568)
  - Check stubs, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 569)
  - Check stubs, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 570)
  - Check stubs, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 571)
  - Check stubs, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 572)
  - Chemical Bank (Box 20, Folder 573)
    Credit notice
  - Copyright (Box 20, Folder 574)
  - Charles, Dick, 1961 May 31 (Box 20, Folder 575)
    Estimate of costs of LP pressing
  - Creative Arts Rehabilitation Center (Box 20, Folder 576)
    Receipt of gift
  - Expo '67 (Box 20, Folder 577)
    Agreement
  - Fine and Dandy (Box 20, Folder 578)
    1930 agreement with Green-Gensler corporation (publishers)
  - Fine and Dandy (Box 20, Folder 579)
    re: transfer of Warburg's rights
  - George Gershwin Song Book, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 580)
    re: Library of Congress
  - Gershwin (Box 20, Folder 581)
    Affidavit and budget for George and Ira Gershwin: Music for stage and film
  - Hampshire Business Services (Box 20, Folder 582)
    Bill
  - Harms (Box 20, Folder 583)
    Agreements and statements of royalties
  - re: Highest Tree (Box 20, Folder 584)
  - Insurance Company of North America (Box 20, Folder 585)
    Policies
  - Irving Trust Company (Box 20, Folder 586)
    Loan for piano
  - Itinerary, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 587)
  - Juilliard School, 1979 Oct. 19 (Box 20, Folder 588)
  - King Brand Music Papers, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 589)
  - Knox, Weaver & Co., 1961 Apr. 26 (Box 21, Folder 590)
    Bill for additional insurance premium
  - Let 'Em Eat Cake (Box 21, Folder 591)
  - Linden and Deutsch, 1971 Apr. 7 (Box 21, Folder 592)
    re: late payment for royalties from Warner Brothers
  - Merkin Hall Concert (Box 21, Folder 593)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 594)
  - Music Publishers Holding Company, 1956-1965 (Box 21, Folder 595)
  - Music Therapy Center, 1977 Apr. 27 (Box 21, Folder 596)
    Receipt for gift
  - Mutual Theatre Ticket Bills, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 596)
    Service
  - NAACP, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 597)
    Pledge form
  - New York (City). Department of Housing, 1969-1988 (Box 21, Folder 598)
    re: rent increase
  - Nola Sound Studios, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 599)
  - One Little Girl (Box 21, Folder 600)
  - re: Painting Collection (Box 21, Folder 601)
  - Paris '90 (Box 21, Folder 602)
  - Pennsylvania Company, 1947-1951 (Box 21, Folder 603)
    Statement of income
  - Porgy and Bess lecture tour (Box 21, Folder 604)
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA) (Box 21, Folder 605)
  - G. Ricordi, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 606)
    Statements
  - Rockhill Radio (Box 21, Folder 607)
  - Samson Music (Box 21, Folder 608)
  - Songs (Can't We Be Friends) (Box 21, Folder 609)
  - Songs (Christmas Eve and Cloudless Blue) (Box 21, Folder 610)
  - Songwriters Guild, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 611)
    Certificate of membership, certificates of renewal, registration forms and bill re: Hunter's Moon
  - Songwriter's Guild, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 612)
    Royalty check stubs
  - Songwriters Protective Association (Box 21, Folder 613)
    re: Moonlight
  - Swaine, Adeney, Brigg & Sons, 1961 Oct. 13 (Box 21, Folder 614)
    Bill for jewelry
  - Taxes, 1950s (Box 21, Folder 615)
  - Taxes, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 616)
  - Taxes, 1970s (Box 22, Folder 617)
  - re: Trust Fund (Box 22, Folder 618)
  - United Medical Service (Box 22, Folder 619)
  - United States Trust, 1946-1955 (Box 22, Folder 620)
  - United States Trust, 1956-1959 (Box 22, Folder 621)
  - United States Trust, 1960-1988 (Box 22, Folder 622)
  - Veterans Administration (Box 22, Folder 623)
  - Warner Bros. (Harms), 1970-1989 (Box 22, Folder 624)
  - Webb Recording Co. (Box 22, Folder 625)
  - White, Weld & Co., 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 626)
- Programs, Publicity, and Clippings, 1930-1986; Series VI; 1' (2 boxes)